

# VINAYAK JOSHI

GRAPHIC DESIGNER | VIDEO EDITOR | UI DESIGNER

133 Ambey Nagar, Behind Ganesh Mandir, Indore, Madhya Pradesh, Postalzip - 452011

**Phone**. +91 - 6267728398

Email. Vinayakjoshi7723@gmail.com

#### PROFESSIONAL STATEMENT

Creative Designer with 5 years of experience in the graphic design industry. Extensive experience with conceptualizing and managing digital marketing campaigns over social media and other mediums. Specializes in rebranding projects, where vast knowledge of logo design, marketing and copywriting can be applied. Drafts own ideas using programs such as Photoshop and Illustrator.

#### **EXPERTISE**

- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Lightroom
- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe InDesign
- / laobe in besig
- Wordpress
- Microsoft Word
- Toon-Boom Harmony

#### SOCIAL

#### Linkedin #01

linkedin.com/in/vinayak-j-5ba38a193

#### Instagram #02

instagram.com/vinayak\_joshi76

#### Facebook #03

facebook.com/vinayak.joshi.94043626

#### Twitter #04

twitter.com/Vinayak64669782

#### **EXPERIENCE**

| April 2018 - May 2019                  | CREATIVE DESIGNER   |
|--|---|
| <b>Surbhi Digital Studio</b><br>Indore | Here I have done all type of Studio related work like Photo Editing, Mug Printing, Flex And Banner Designing etc. |
| Mariana Cartanahan asa                 |   |

#### May 2019 - September 2019 GRAPHIC DESIGNER AND CATALOGUER

| etaDit <sup>®</sup> |  |
|---------------------|--|
| Indore              |  |

In this company I have learnt Graphic Design and how to product listing on Amazon, Walmart, Shopify, Etsy, Ebay etc.

#### February 2020 - March 2021 GRAPHIC DESIGNER AND CATALOGUER



Indore

In this company I have learnt Graphic Design and made banner of Noon ( UAE Based Comapany ).

#### April 2021 - February 2022

## GRAPHIC DESIGNER AND UI/UX DESIGNER



Indore

NewsBytes is India's only explanatory news portal, designed for mobile-first audience. Here I have learnt UI and UX design skills.

### **PROJECTS**

#### **Design Website**

Betdaddys.com Elitehomestore.com ourrhomeappliances.com

#### February 22 - September 22

Q DIGOPTIMIZER

## ember 22 GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Indore

Digioptimizer is a marketing agency that uses multiple platforms for providing solutions to all the marketing needs of small and medium organizations.

## **HOBBIES**

- Learning new languages like Arabic And Japanese.
  - **Reason**: To learn typography.
- Learning new softwares like Toon Boom Harmony and Blender.
- Playing Open World Games Like "Genshin Impact".

## **EDUCATION**

| 2017              | High School ( 10 <sup>th</sup> )                          |
|-------------------|---|
| Motherland School | I have done my High school in 2017 with Science and Maths |
| Indore            | Stream.   |
| 2019              | Higher Secondary School                                   |
| Motherland School | I have done my High secondary school in 2019 with         |
| Indore            | Science and Maths Stream                                  |